geekstoy.com 2014-04-15

# Betfair Trading and Sports Betting Forum - View Single Post - Privacy Policy

**_Overview_**  
This privacy policy sets out how Talented Mavericks Limited uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website or our products. Any information you provide by which you can be identified when using this website or our software prodcuts, will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Talented Mavericks Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 21st September 2009.

**_What we collect_**  
For the purposes of account management and technical support, we may collect the following information, either directly via our website or software products, or indirectly via payment processing services or other third party applications.

• Name  
• Contact details including email address(s)  
• IP Address and Geographic location.  
• System configuration info. { EG Operating system version, regional settings, browser version }  
• Product configuration info.  
• Application usage data. { EG Log ins, log outs, application errors. }

In very limited circumstances when you contact us for support, we may ask you for your Betfair or Betdaq user name to enable us to identify you or communicate with the exchange to resolve your issue.

**_What we do not collect_**  
We do not collect any personal information held by Betfair or Betdaq including but not limited to passwords, account balances, betting activity, email addresses or payment info. We do not collect any files or personal information from your system other than items specified above.

**_Security_**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

**_How your Personal Information will be used?_**  
We will process your Personal Information in order to allow you access and make use of our products or website, to allow you to participate in the services offered, to administer your account, to maintain our accounts and records, to monitor website usage levels and the quality of the service we provide and to inform you, from time to time of essential communications regarding products, a periodic newsletter and also about products and services that we consider may interest you and for related purposes. 

**_To whom and where personal information may be disclosed?  
_**Your Personal Information may for the purposes described above, be transferred subject to appropriate agreement to third parties, for the processing of that Personal Information on our behalf. From time to time, we may retain third parties to process your Personal Information for the purposes listed above and such processing will be governed by a contract in the form required by law.

Where required by law, your Personal Information may also be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory, sporting or enforcement authority. For the purposes of support, where we deem it appropriate, your Personal Information may be disclosed to Betfair or Betdaq. We may also at our discretion either contact you, or disclose your details to business associates within the industry where we have been provided specific evidence of anonymous abuse or libel on your part.

We will not sell, or disclose your information to third parties for any purpose other than specified above.

**_Mailing List Inclusion / Opt Out_**  
When accessing our products or forums, you may be automatically subscribed to our mailing list. It is a condition of using our products or forums that you are subscribed to our mailing list to enable us to communicate with you effectively. Should you no longer wish to use our products or forums and wish to opt out of the mailing list, [you can do so by following the instructions here.](http://www.geekstoy.com/forum/showthread.php?p=74608#post74608)

**_How we may use Cookies on our Site and what Information we collect_**  
Although we do not use, process or store cookies or information related to them directly, 3rd party products such as the forums may use them for identification / statistical / internal operating purposes. { EG When you tell the forums you wish to remain logged in, this is handled via a cookie on your PC. }
